The death of an icon comes to life
Soaked in Bleach is a music, drama, documentary
film directed by Benjamin Statler.
Twenty years ago, Kurt Cobain was found dead of an
apparent gunshot wound to the head.
The world was told it was a suicide, but evidence would lead
many people to believe it might be otherwise.
The film investigates the possibilities that exist that Kurt Cobain's death might not have been a suicide, that the Seattle Police Department rushed their verdict, and the global media perpetuated
lies and misinformation fed to them by Courtney Love that created the belief in many that Cobain killed himself—but when revealed to be lies—lead many to now question what happened.
Tom Grant, played by Daniel Roebuck.
Courtney Love, played by Sarah Scott.
Dylan Carson, played by August Emerson.
Himself, played by Kurt Loder.
Kurt Cobain, played by Tyler Bryan.
Rosemary Carroll, played by Julie Lancaster.
Soaked in Bleach is a 2015 American docudrama directed by Benjamin Statler, who
co-wrote and produced it with Richard Middelton and Donnie Eichar.
The film details the events leading up to the death of Kurt Cobain, as seen through the perspective of Tom Grant, the
private detective who was hired by Courtney Love to find Cobain, shortly before his death in 1994.
It also explores the theory that Cobain's death was not a suicide.
The film stars Tyler Bryan as Cobain and Daniel Roebuck as Grant, with Sarah
Scott portraying Courtney Love and August Emerson as Dylan Carlson.
The film explores themes of private investigator,
gunshot wound, reneactment, possible suicide.
The tone is emotional.